<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Apple Hot News</title>
		<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
		<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2003, Apple Computer, Inc.</copyright>
		<webMaster>rss-feeds@apple.com</webMaster>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2004 15:15:01 PST</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2004 15:15:01 PST</lastBuildDate>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<generator>In house</generator>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs>
		<item>
			<title>New &amp;#147;Star Wars Trilogy&amp;#148; Shines on DVD</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/pro/</link>
			<description>The re-mastering of the &amp;#147;Star Wars Trilogy&amp;#148; involved epic wrangling of badly degraded master prints by film restoration expert John Lowry of Lowry Digital Images. [Oct 08]</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Murch Using Final Cut Pro HD for &amp;#147;Jarhead&amp;#148;</title>
			<link>http://www.reuters.co.uk/newsPackageArticle.jhtml?type=entertainmentNews&amp;storyID=597271&amp;section=news</link>
			<description>For Hollywood Reporter, Sheigh Crabtree writes that Oscar-winning editor Walter Murch &amp;#147;will reteam his key editing crew from &amp;#145;Cold Mountain&amp;#146; and again use Apple&amp;#146;s Final Cut Pro system, but in high definition&amp;#148; for the editing of Universal Pictures&amp;#146; upcoming Gulf War drama &amp;#147;Jarhead.&amp;#148; [Oct 06]</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mac OS X Tip of the Week: Moving Windows</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/pro/tips/</link>
			<description>Ever experience &amp;#147;window overload&amp;#148;? Learn how to easily move non-active window behind the window you&amp;#146;re working with by checking out the latest Mac OS X killer tip at the Apple Pro/ site. [Oct 05]</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>iMac G5: &amp;#147;Marvel on the Inside, too&amp;#148;</title>
			<link>http://www.freep.com/money/tech/mwendland5e_20041005.htm</link>
			<description>&amp;#147;The new G5 iMac is the finest personal computer I&amp;#146;ve ever used, hands down,&amp;#148; writes Mike Wendland for the Detroit Free Press. &amp;#147;Nothing comes close. If you have ever thought of switching from a Windows-based PC to a Mac, this is the deal-clincher. It is simply a stunning machine both to look at and to use.&amp;#148; [Oct 05]</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Turning the Tables Using CSS</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/pro/words/meyer/</link>
			<description>Have you noticed web pages loading a bit faster than usual? You might thank Eric Meyer, an expert and author on the subject of Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) &amp;#151; a standards-based method of coding websites to make them work more efficiently with today&amp;#146;s Internet browsers. [Oct 04]</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>iMac G5: &amp;#147;even more exquisite than last one&amp;#148;</title>
			<link>http://www.forbes.com/infoimaging/feeds/infoimaging/2004/09/30/infoimagingusatoday_2004_09_30_eng-usatoday_money_eng-usatoday_money_034721_4723222365328148192.html</link>
			<description>&amp;#147;This latest head turner manages to better its clever predecessor in design &amp;#151; no small achievement,&amp;#148; writes Edward C. Baig for USA Today. &amp;#147;The back of the computer is elegant in its simplicity. You can loosen three captive screws to remove the cover to add, say, extra memory, or a wireless AirPort networking card.&amp;#148; [Sep 30]</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Apple Unveils Logic Pro 7</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/logic/</link>
			<description>Logic Pro 7, the next major release of the award-winning professional music creation and audio production software, will change the way musicians and audio engineers worldwide compose, record, edit and mix music in any studio environment. In addition to more than 100 workflow enhancements, breakthrough new software instruments, new mastering plug-ins and support for Apple Loops, Logic Pro 7 also debuts distributed audio processing, a revolutionary technology which allows audio pros to tap into a virtually unlimited number of Macs to expand available Digital Signal Processing (DSP) power. [Sep 29]</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Apple Debuts Logic Express 7</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/software/logicexpress</link>
			<description>Logic Express 7, a streamlined version of Logic, provides a basic set of professional tools for students, educators and advanced hobbyists at an affordable price. [Sep 29]</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Introducing Two New Jam Packs</title>
			<link>http://www.apple.com/ilife/garageband/jampacks/</link>
			<description>Apple introduces two new Jam Packs for its GarageBand music creation software, giving musicians and aspiring musicians more Apple Loops and software instruments to create music. Jam Pack 2: Remix Tools makes it easy to produce compelling dance, hip-hop and electronica tracks, while Jam Pack 3: Rhythm Section offers songwriters a complete backing band for their rock, alternative and country music. [Sep 29]</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>.Mac Increases Email &amp;amp; iDisk Storage</title>
			<link>http://www.mac.com</link>
			<description>.Mac, the popular suite of Internet software and services, now offers both new members and its more than half million existing members 250MB of combined online storage for .Mac mailboxes and iDisk folders, perfect for sharing photos, movies and documents with family, friends and coworkers. Sign up now for a free 60-day trial. [Sep 29]</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
